profitstars.com 2019-08-13

# Privacy Policy

Jack Henry & Associates, Inc. (“ **Company** ” or “ **We** ”) respect your privacy and are committed to protecting it through our compliance with this policy.

### Children Under the A​ge of 13

Our Websites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may provide any information to or on the Websites. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information on the Websites or on or through any of its features. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at:

663 W. Hwy 60 P.O. Box 807  
Monett, MO 65708-8215 

### ​Information We Collect About You and How We Collect It

We collect several types of information from and about users of our Websites, including information:

  * by which you may be personally identified, such as name, postal address, e-mail address, telephone number, or any other identifier by which you may be contacted online or offline (“ **personal information** ”);  

  * that is about you but individually does not identify you; and/or  

  * about your internet connection, the equipment you use to access our Websites and usage details.  

We collect this information:  

  * Directly from you when you provide it to us.  

  * Automatically as you navigate through the site. Information collected automatically may include usage details, IP addresses, and information collected through cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies.  

  * From third parties, for example, our business partners.  

### Information You Provi​de to Us. The information we collect on or through our Websites may include:

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our Websites. This includes information provided at the time of registering to use our Websites, subscribing   
to our service, posting material, or requesting further services. We may also ask you for information when you enter a contest or promotion sponsored by us,   
and when you report a problem with our Websites.
  * Records and copies of your correspondence (including email addresses), if you contact us.
  * Your responses to surveys that we might ask you to complete for research purposes.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our Websites and of the fulfillment of your orders. You may be required to provide financial information before   
placing an order through our Websites.
  * Your search queries on the Websites.

You also may provide information to be published or displayed (hereinafter, “ **posted** ”) on public areas of the Websites or transmitted to other users of the Websites or third parties (collectively, “ **User Contributions** ”). Your User Contributions are posted on and transmitted to others at your own risk. Although we limit access to certain pages, please be aware that no security measures are perfect or impenetrable. Additionally, we cannot control the actions of other users of the Websites with whom you may choose to share your User Contributions. Therefore, we cannot and do not guarantee that your User Contributions will not be viewed by unauthorized persons.

### Information We Collect Through Au​tomatic Data Collection Technologies

As you navigate through and interact with our Websites, we may use automatic data collection technologies to collect certain information about your equipment, browsing actions, and patterns, including:​

  * ​Details of your visits to our Websites, including traffic data, location data, logs, and other communication data and the resources that you access and use on the Websites.
  * Information about your computer and internet connection, including your IP address, operating system, and browser type.

We also may use these technologies to collect information about your online activities over time and across third-party websites or other online services (behavioral tracking). [Click here](http://optout.aboutads.info/) for information on how you can opt out of behavioral tracking on the websites and how we respond to web browser signals and other mechanisms that enable consumers to exercise choice about behavioral tracking.

The information we collect automatically may include personal information or we may maintain it or associate it with personal information we collect in other ways or receive from third parties. It helps us to improve our Websites and to deliver a better and more personalized service, including by enabling us to:

  * ​Estimate our audience size and usage patterns.
  * Store information about your preferences, allowing us to customize our Websites according to your individual interests.
  * Speed up your searches.
  * Recognize you when you return to our Websites.

The technologies we use for this automatic data collection may include: 

  * **Cookies (or browser cookies).** A cookie is a small file placed on the hard drive of your computer. You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating   
the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Websites. Unless you have   
adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you direct your browser to our Websites.  

  * **Flash Cookies.** Certain features of our Websites may use local stored objects (or Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from, and on our Websites. Flash cookies are not managed by the same browser settings as are used for browser cookies. For information about managing your privacy and security settings for Flash cookies, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.  

  * **Web Beacons.** Pages of our Websites and our emails may contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs, pixel tags, and single-pixel gifs) that permit the Company, for example, to count users who have visited those pages or opened an email and for other related website statistics (for example, recording the popularity of certain website content and verifying system and server integrity).  

> ### ​Third-Party Use of Cookies and Other Tracking Technologies

Some content or applications, including advertisements, on the Websites are served by third-parties, including advertisers, ad networks and servers, content providers, and application providers. These third parties may use cookies alone or in conjunction with web beacons or other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you use our websites. The information they collect may be associated with your personal information or they may collect information, including personal information, about your online activities over time and across different websites and other online services. They may use this information to provide you with interest-based (behavioral) advertising or other targeted content.

We do not control these third parties' tracking technologies or how they may be used. If you have any questions about an advertisement or other targeted content, you should contact the responsible provider directly. For information about how you can opt out of receiving targeted advertising from many providers, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Inform​ation.

### How We Use Your Inform​ation

We use information that we collect about you or that you provide to us, including any personal information:

  * To present our Websites and its contents to you.  

  * To provide you with information, products, or services that you request from us.  

  * To fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it.  

  * To provide you with notices about your account, including expiration and renewal notices.  

  * To carry out our obligations and enforce our rights arising from any contracts entered into between you and us, including for billing and collection.  

  * To notify you about changes to our Websites or any products or services we offer or provide though it.  

  * To allow you to participate in interactive features on our Websites.  

  * In any other way we may describe when you provide the information.  

  * For any other purpose with your consent.  

We may also use your information to contact you about our own and third-parties' goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you do not want us to use   
your information in this way, please check the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form). For more information, see   
Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.

We may use the information we have collected from you to enable us to display advertisements to our advertisers' target audiences. Even though we do not disclose  
your personal information for these purposes without your consent, if you click on or otherwise interact with an advertisement, the advertiser may assume that   
you meet its target criteria.

### Disclosure of Yo​ur Information

We may disclose aggregated information about our users without restriction.

We may disclose personal information that we collect or you provide as described in this privacy policy:

  * To our subsidiaries and affiliates.
  * To contractors, service providers, and other third parties we use to support our business and who are bound by contractual obligations to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them.
  * To a buyer or other successor in the event of a merger, divestiture, restructuring, reorganization, dissolution, or other sale or transfer of some or all of   
Jack Henry & Associates, Inc.'s assets, whether as a going concern or as part of bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, in which personal information   
held by Jack Henry & Associates, Inc. about our Websites users is among the assets transferred.  

  * To third parties to market their products or services to you if you have not opted out of these disclosures. We contractually require these third parties to keep personal information confidential and use it only for the purposes for which we disclose it to them. For more information, see Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Information.  

  * To fulfill the purpose for which you provide it. For example, if you give us an email address to use the “email a friend” feature of our Websites, we will transmit   
the contents of that email and your email address to the recipients.  

  * For any other purpose disclosed by us when you provide the information.  

  * With your consent.  

  * We may also disclose your personal information:  

  * To comply with any court order, law, or legal process, including to respond to any government or regulatory request.  

  * To enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements, including for billing and collection purposes.  

  * If we believe disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Jack Henry & Associates, Inc., our customers, or others.  

### Choices About How We Use and Disclose Your Infor​mation

We strive to provide you with choices regarding the personal information you provide to us. We have created mechanisms to provide you with the following control over your information: 

  * **Tracking Technologies and Advertising.** You can set your browser to refuse all or some browser cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. To learn how you can manage your Flash cookie settings, visit the Flash player settings page on Adobe's website. If you disable or refuse cookies, please note that some parts of this site may then be inaccessible or not function properly.  

  * **Disclosure of Your Information for Third-Party Advertising.** If you do not want us to share your personal information with unaffiliated or non-agent third   
parties for promotional purposes, you can opt out by sending an email stating your request to [jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com](mailto:%20jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com).  

  * **Promotional Offers from the Company.** If you do not wish to have your contact information used by the Company to promote our own or third parties' products or services, you can opt out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form) or at any other time by sending us an email stating your request to [jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com](mailto:%20jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com). If we have sent you a promotional email, you may send us a return email asking to be  
omitted from future email distributions.  

  * **Targeted Advertising.** If you do not want us to use information that we collect or that you provide to us to deliver advertisements according to our advertisers' target-audience preferences, you can opt out by checking the relevant box located on the form on which we collect your data (the registration form) or at any   
other time by sending us an email stating your request to [jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com](mailto:%20jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com).  

We do not control third parties' collection or use of your information to serve interest-based advertising. However, these third parties may provide you with ways to  
choose not to have your information collected or used in this way. You can opt out of receiving targeted ads from members of the Network Advertising Initiative (“ **NAI** ”) on the NAI's website.

###  ​Your Californ​ia Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section § 1798.83 permits users of our Websites that are California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please send an email to [jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com](mailto:jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com) or write us at:   
663 W. Hwy 60 P.O. Box 807, Monett, Missouri 65708-8215.

### Data Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration, and disclosure. All information you provide to us is stored on our secure servers behind firewalls.

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. Where we have given you (or where you have chosen) a password for access to certain parts of our Websites, you are responsible for keeping this password confidential. We ask you not to share your password with anyone.

Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet is not completely secure. Although we do our best to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee the security of your personal information transmitted to our Websites. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk. We are not responsible for circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Websites.  

### Changes to Our Privacy Po​licy

It is our policy to post any changes we make to our privacy policy on this page with a notice that the privacy policy has been updated on the Websites home page. If we make material changes to how we treat our users' personal information, we will notify you through a notice on the Websites home page. The date the privacy policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for ensuring we have an up-to-date active and deliverable email address for you, and for periodically visiting our Websites and this privacy policy to check for any changes.

### Contact Information

To ask questions or comment about this privacy policy and our privacy practices, contact us at:

663 W. Hwy 60 P.O. Box 807  
Monett, MO 65708-8215  
[jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com​](mailto:%20jhaprivacypolicy@jackhenry.com)​​​​​
